hey everyone thanks for listening to The
Grow Your Life podcast my name is
Jeremiah Kowski and in this podcast I
talk about ways for you to grow your
mentorship coaching training and
speaking business how to make tens of
millions of dollars online or even if
you just want to make a few thousand
dollars how to get started the right way
I did a mastermind this weekend spoke
for two days straight and came away with
a lot of really great information I
wanted to share with you on this podcast
one of the number one things that
resonated with the people that we're
talking to that I think is going to be
really impactful for you is the idea of
making faster decisions and I think that
this is something that people way too
often avoid and ignore and it's such a
powerful success strategy in our society
today we're taught to be super cautious
super careful tiptoe around things be
very um you know don't jump until you
know for certain that something's going
to produce a result successful business
owners millionaires six figure earners
they make decisions fast they don't sit
on a decision and the problem is this
business is hard takes a long time to
actually get stuff
done like even if you made super fast
decisions it's still going to take you a
long time to accomplish things and by
taking longer and delaying the
inevitable with your decisions as a
business owner you're not going to make
things happen faster because you're more
accurate with your decisions that's a
big
false belief and a lie that people think
is if I can make perfect decisions then
I can make sure that I'm more successful
in fact it it kind of seems like that's
what you would do to be successful
because otherwise we don't want to make
the wrong decisions we want to make sure
that they're the right ones the problem
is this is that if we're taking a long
time to delay decisions it's better to
make an imperfect decision today than to
push off a decision to next week I
promise promise you that promise you
that in your business and this is one of
the biggest mistakes I think a lot of
people make is that they're they're so
worried about making things work out the
way that they see it of course we want
things to work out we want them to come
together but sitting on a an
idea and and part of it could also be
fear of missing out where you're afraid
to decide on one idea because there's
three others that might be just as good
it takes deciding on something even if
it might not be quote unquote the best
and listen you can come up with a
thousand million one reasons why it's
not the best and delaying things is
better that is not going to make you
successful it's not going to make you
financially successful it's not going to
protect you and so it's really an
amazing thing as our brains are wiring
us and telling us that it's for our own
good that we're going to delay our
decisions we're going to make sure that
they're perfect
we're not going to take too much risk
things like that when in fact taking
risky decisions without all the evidence
without all the
facts this is coming from somebody by
the way who is what's called a fact
finder I need to have all the facts
before making decisions and I've had to
train myself it's okay to jump and
actually use the decision to make better
decisions here's why because you can
make an initial decision and as soon as
you make that decision new data starts
to come into your atmosphere when we
delay a decision all we're doing is
guessing we're guessing how something
might go and you might even be guessing
based off of past experience or
experience from other people it's still
guessing and so you can't really have
any actual evidence of what's going to
work your fact finding isn't even going
to be effective until you take riskier
decisions that's the paradigm shift and
I think that's what's stopping so many
coaches and mentors from being
successful they taking way too long to
decide to take action to plan their
actions when in fact they would do
better to just take less than perfect
action and tweak and just and course
correct it along the way I get that this
might not be natural for you I get that
this might not be how you've always done
things
okay you know especially if if you are
not a major risk-taker
personality one of
the greatest activities that you can do
that's going to make you more successful
is faster imperfect
decisions taking more imperfect action
training yourself even if it's hard even
if it's
uncomfortable to Leap
Forward you know I I see people
T to this day they've been in my
coaching group for over a year and they
still have not made a decision to launch
something yet and I asked them why and
it's always because they came up with a
better idea and this is one of the
problems that people make is they they
make a decision to come up with a better
idea when in fact putting something out
there growing an audience getting real
people in front of you and actually
connecting with people is the only way
to really grow a coaching training and
mentorship business if you don't have
people in front of you to actually coach
trainer Mentor how do you expect to have
a
business okay so we can start off by
connecting with people through our
social media through our email lists we
can host live Zoom calls we can host
events where we connect with people we
do Q&A we do a VIP session the goal is
this to gather as much data and
information as you can about the target
Prospect
because here's here's a truth that you
might not realize no matter how much
experience you have you don't know
everything about the people that you're
working with you just
don't I've been in this industry for two
decades and I still don't know
everything about the people that I'm
working with and every single month I'm
learning new things every six months I
notice a major pattern shift in the
direction of how I'm marketing selling
training and coaching in my business to
improve you know we've had a massive
shift happened in just the last month in
the direction that we've taken a lot of
our content a lot of how I talk and
communicate I'm way more confident now
in how I communicate I'm as confident
I'm the most confident that I've ever
been and it comes from a very authentic
place but it started by me taking
imperfect action even when I didn't
quote un feel quote feel so confident
that's what actually got me here I
didn't wait until I felt this way today
what got me feeling confident is taking
unconfident slightly delusion
action
overall stepping into the impostor
syndrome actually embracing the idea of
the impostor syndrome and I was
listening to a podcast the other day a
comedian was on Joe Rogan and he said
every time that he steps onto a new
stage at a new level where he goes maybe
from a music hall to a
stadium impostor syndrome strikes why am
I here I don't deserve to be here and in
fact that is his clue to know that he's
stepping into the next Direction and Joe
Joe agreed with him he said anybody
who's done great things actually is the
impostor when they show up see this is
the problem that most people make is
they're waiting until everything is
perfect that they got all the
achievements and the accolades and
everything's working out when in fact
it's just a simple decision to show up
in your power and it's a decision to not
let any of what anybody thinks about you
stop you from being the best most
powerful version of yourself I believe
that anybody who's listening to this
right now can make six figures in a
business if you don't believe that about
yourself that's what's going to stop you
nothing else and you can change your
beliefs about yourself you know I was
talking to a lady this past week she
said that she felt like she struggled to
make six figures because she hasn't made
six
figures um yeah just basic math
everybody who's made six and seven
figures at one time never made it and
they made a decision to step out and to
do things that would put six figures and
seven figures in their bank
account they didn't wait until they felt
good enough to do so or achieve
something unfortunately our academic
system has lied to people and created
this gatekeeping where you don't deserve
and aren't allowed to teach and you
aren't allowed
to step into a higher level until you
you quote unquote reach certain
accolades and Milestones I think that's
one of the most dangerous deadly things
that's happened in our culture and our
society today is that we don't really
support promoting people to higher
levels no of
course there's a there's a deeper
conversation to
this you you are always going to start
off and not feel like you're at 100%
you're when you're starting out that's
the rub that's the thing that a lot of
people they're waiting until they feel
good enough they're waiting until they
feel 100% to finally put themselves out
there when in fact feeling like 50% or
even 30% is when you need to put
yourself out
there and that is what will transform
your life your business and your
income making faster decisions stop
waiting until the stars align perfectly
or things come to together perfectly
stop letting your pride your ego your
judgment towards other people you know
maybe you judge other people who quote
unquote claim to be able to do things
but haven't quote unquote accomplished
it in their
life or maybe you quote unquote judge
other people who flippantly make
decisions quickly with lack lack of
evidence I'm
sorry but that's what's stopping you
from being successful
financially and I can say this with
confidence of working with thousands of
coaches trainers and mentors that when
you can when you can literally rewire
your brain to not operate this way as
the norm and you take faster decisions
and you stop waiting until all the
situations are perfect according to what
everybody else around you is telling you
Society tells you that you can only move
forward until you've checked off certain
Milestones Society tells you you can
only make a decision once you've checked
off certain mileston zones I'm here to
tell you that that is a madeup invented
structure that you do not have to
operate in if you so choose not to now
if you want to operate in it go ahead
but you're going to delay yourself from
actually being successful from actually
making the kind of money that you want
to make and unfortunately that becomes
an addiction to
learning and you have an aversion to
actually doing anything with what you're
learning because you become so caught up
in the learning process us and avoidant
of actually doing something and that's
an issue that goes on inside of our head
I had this issue for the longest time by
the way I did I'm saying this to
somebody like who has been there done
this lived the life bought the
T-shirt has the proof and the
receipts okay so I'm not just saying
this as like a like some weird random
opinion that I'm somebody
who looking back at the last 5 years 10
years 20 years that I've been in this
industry I could have been a millionaire
20 years
ago literally there is no reason I
couldn't knowing what I know today 20
years ago if I did
it I even tried like three or four
times now of course it took me that
amount of time it doesn't have to take
you that long it was my fear it was my
worry it was me not believing in myself
it was me being so concerned with what
everybody thought about me and doing the
quote unquote right things that
everybody says that I should do and
being a good
boy and checking off all the
boxes putting the Stars on my chore
chart to say that I did all the things I
should believing that then I deserve
some kind of success uccess and the
truth is that doesn't make you any more
deserving that stops you from being
successful if I could do it all over
again I would do exactly what I'm
telling you right now make faster
decisions stop waiting until you feel
ready you'll get ready by taking action
before you feel
ready in this business that's what's
going to take you to a quarter million
and a half a million and beond
I'd love to be able to Mentor you in
this listen if you're not part of my
client growth accelerator program get on
the waiting list the doors open couple
times a year when we do open the doors
again I'd love to have you join us as
well every couple of months we host live
free events they're exclusive training
events where I pull back the curtain on
what's working and dive deep into a
specific topic that's going to help take
you from where you are to where you want
to be and be successful in a business
and so I'd love to have you join me if
you see me marketing or advertising one
of these Live Events register for it
join us and I can't wait to help you
become a six and then eventually seven
figure business owner we'll talk soon
have a good one go your
[Music]
[Applause]
life